( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Check
يفحص
how that video of Xie Xinxu got leaked.
كيف تم تسريب فيديو شي شينشو؟
I'll go by Huayuehui
سأستخدم اسم هوايوهوي
and pick up the suit you need for tomorrow's meeting.
واستلم البدلة التي تحتاجها لاجتماع الغد.
[Xu]
[Xu]
[Xie Xinxu [95 messages] Xie Xinxu]
[شيه شينكسو [95 رسالة] شيه شينكسو]
Could it really be just like my brother said?
هل يمكن أن يكون الأمر حقاً كما قال أخي؟
That Xie Xinxu got close to me
لقد اقترب مني شي شينشو
only because he wanted to use me?
فقط لأنه أراد استغلالي؟
Xie Xinxu.
شيه شينكسو.
Can I still trust you?
هل ما زلت أثق بك؟
[Nongyu] Feeling a little down.
[نونغيو] أشعر ببعض الحزن.
Want to come to Huayuehui for some milk tea?
هل ترغب في القدوم إلى هوايوهوي لتناول بعض شاي الحليب؟
[Yiyi] I really wish I could fly back and have it.
[ييي] أتمنى حقاً أن أتمكن من العودة بالطائرة والحصول عليه.
But I'm out of town doing field research.
لكنني خارج المدينة أقوم بأبحاث ميدانية.
Are you holding up okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Mr. Wu.
السيد وو.
Your delivery.
توصيل طلبك.
Alright. Thank you.
حسنًا. شكرًا لك.
[[News Alert] A sudden fire has broken out on Huayuehui Commercial Street!]
[[تنبيه إخباري] اندلع حريق مفاجئ في شارع هوايوهوي التجاري!]
[Emergency rescue operations are in progress]
[عمليات الإنقاذ الطارئة جارية]
[Xiang]
[شيانغ]
Yiyi, I can't reach Nongyu.
ييي، لا أستطيع الوصول إلى نونغيو.
Is she with you?
هل هي معك؟
No.
لا.
But she messaged me about ten minutes ago,
لكنها راسلتني قبل حوالي عشر دقائق،
saying she was heading to Huayuehui for milk tea.
وقالت إنها متجهة إلى هوايوهوي لتناول شاي الحليب.
And now there's suddenly a fire there.
وفجأة اندلع حريق هناك.
I can't get through to her either.
لا أستطيع الوصول إليها أيضاً.
[Little Bunny Dry Cleaners]
[مغسلة ليتل باني للتنظيف الجاف]
Don't come any closer.
لا تقترب أكثر.
Step back.
تراجع للخلف.
Keep moving back.
استمر في التراجع.
Madam.
سيدتي.
Has Li Xiang been here?
هل زار لي شيانغ هذا المكان؟
No.
لا.
[Flammable]
[قابل للاشتعال]
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Just as I thought.
كما توقعت تماماً.
The dog I raised
الكلب الذي ربيته
will always protect its master.
سيحمي سيده دائماً.
I knew you wouldn't submit so easily.
كنت أعرف أنك لن تستسلم بهذه السهولة.
But that doesn't matter.
لكن هذا لا يهم.
I can help you.
أستطيع مساعدتك.
Usually,
عادة،
you need to do something at least a hundred times
عليك أن تفعل شيئًا ما مئة مرة على الأقل
before it becomes
قبل أن يصبح
muscle memory.
الذاكرة العضلية.
But given what you're capable of,
لكن بالنظر إلى ما أنت قادر عليه،
fifty rounds should have been enough, right?
كان ينبغي أن تكون خمسون جولة كافية، أليس كذلك؟
Now,
الآن،
let's see how well you've learned it.
لنرى مدى إتقانك لها.
Are you sure you've ever really tamed me?
هل أنت متأكد من أنك قد روّضتني حقاً؟
So far,
حتى الآن،
only Nongyu has managed it.
نونغيو هي الوحيدة التي نجحت في ذلك.
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
Because now Nongyu already knows
لأن نونغيو يعرف الآن بالفعل
that you got close to her just to get back at me.
أنك تقربت منها فقط للانتقام مني.
So why don't you come and beg me
فلماذا لا تأتي وتتوسل إلي؟
to put in a good word for you?
هل تريد أن تتوسط لك؟
Even someone like you can grow attached to Ren.
حتى شخص مثلك يمكن أن يتعلق برين.
Nongyu even more so.
نونغيو أكثر من ذلك.
I'm very confident about what we have.
أنا واثق جداً مما لدينا.
My phone ran out of battery,
نفدت بطارية هاتفي،
and I didn't even get my milk tea.
ولم أحصل حتى على شاي الحليب.
Excuse me,
اعذرني،
do you have a power bank?
هل لديك شاحن متنقل؟
Li Xiang?
لي شيانغ؟
You don't need to put on that concerned look.
لا داعي لأن تتظاهر بالقلق.
It's not your brother's money being spent.
إنها ليست أموال أخيك التي تُنفق.
My brother admitted your relationship to me.
اعترف لي أخي بعلاقتكما.
After hiding it for so long,
بعد إخفائه لفترة طويلة،
Wu Siyuan really is a terrible boyfriend.
وو سييوان حبيب سيء للغاية.
You didn't even give a heads-up
لم تُعطِ حتى إشعاراً مسبقاً
before marrying someone your brother hates,
قبل الزواج من شخص يكرهه أخوك،
and nearly driving him crazy.
وكاد ذلك أن يجعله يجن.
That makes you a pretty terrible sister too.
هذا يجعلكِ أختًا سيئة للغاية أيضًا.
So anyone who loves siblings as awful as us
لذا، أي شخص يحب إخوة سيئين مثلنا، فليتفضل بزيارتنا.
must have it really hard.
لا بد أن الأمر صعب للغاية.
Why don't
لماذا لا
you think it through again?
هل فكرت في الأمر مرة أخرى؟
You're the one who should think carefully.
أنت من يجب أن يفكر ملياً.
Xie Xinxu is only using you.
شي شينشو يستغلك فقط.
You can't even see that much clearly,
لا يمكنك حتى أن ترى ذلك بوضوح،
and you'll end up getting your brother killed.
وسينتهي بك الأمر إلى التسبب في مقتل أخيك.
Is there anything in this world
هل يوجد شيء في هذا العالم؟
harder to keep fair than
من الصعب الحفاظ على العدالة أكثر من
what I'm dealing with right now?
ما الذي أواجهه الآن؟
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
Because now Nongyu already knows
لأن نونغيو يعرف الآن بالفعل
that you got close to her just to get back at me.
أنك تقربت منها فقط للانتقام مني.
Hey.
يا.
Nongyu got back to me.
ردت نونغيو عليّ.
She said she's home now
قالت إنها في المنزل الآن
and she's safe.
وهي بأمان.
Okay.
تمام.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
How did you end up like this?
كيف انتهى بك الأمر هكذا؟
I'll get the first aid kit.
سأحضر حقيبة الإسعافات الأولية.
Why didn't you answer your phone or reply to my messages?
لماذا لم ترد على هاتفك أو رسائلي؟
Are you still trying to push me away now?
هل ما زلت تحاول إبعادي الآن؟
So you believed what Wu Siyuan told you.
إذن صدقت ما قاله لك وو سيوان.
That I'm using you, right?
أنا أستغلك، أليس كذلك؟
You should know by now.
كان ينبغي أن تعرف ذلك الآن.
Xie Xinxu's real purpose in approaching you.
ما هو الهدف الحقيقي من تقرب شي شينكسو منك؟
It was only to get revenge on me.
كان ذلك فقط للانتقام مني.
He will not love you.
لن يحبك.
I more or less know what went on between you and my brother.
أعرف إلى حد كبير ما حدث بينك وبين أخي.
Today, it suddenly feels like I don't know him at all.
اليوم، أشعر فجأة وكأنني لا أعرفه على الإطلاق.
And the same goes for you.
وينطبق الأمر نفسه عليك.
You feel like a stranger to me too.
أشعر أنا أيضاً بأنك غريب عني.
So I couldn't help but start doubting
لذا لم أستطع إلا أن أبدأ بالتشكيك.
why you got close to me in the first place.
لماذا اقتربت مني في المقام الأول؟
I really did want to get back at Wu Siyuan.
كنت أرغب حقاً في الانتقام من وو سييوان.
Don't.
لا.
Don't?
لا؟
Why not?
ولم لا؟
Is it because at his core, your brother isn't a bad person,
هل ذلك لأن أخاك ليس شخصاً سيئاً في جوهره؟
and it's just his family background
وهذا مجرد جزء من خلفيته العائلية
that led him to make mistakes?
ما الذي دفعه لارتكاب الأخطاء؟
Or is it because
أم أن ذلك بسبب
no matter how badly he treats other people,
بغض النظر عن مدى سوء معاملته للآخرين،
but to you,
أما أنت،
he's still the perfect brother in every way, right?
لا يزال الأخ المثالي بكل معنى الكلمة، أليس كذلك؟
As long as they are Ren,
طالما أنهم رين،
they do not have normal human emotions.
إنهم لا يملكون مشاعر إنسانية طبيعية.
Their greatest value is to be used as weapons.
تكمن قيمتها الكبرى في استخدامها كأسلحة.
Once they are worn out,
بمجرد أن تبلى،
they are discarded.
يتم التخلص منها.
So what exactly are you planning to do to my brother?
إذن ما الذي تخطط لفعله بأخي بالضبط؟
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Good question.
سؤال جيد.
I really do have plenty of ways to deal with him.
لدي بالفعل العديد من الطرق للتعامل معه.
But unfortunately,
لكن لسوء الحظ،
from the moment I first set my sights on you,
منذ اللحظة التي وقعت عيناي عليكِ فيها لأول مرة،
I had no idea you were his sister.
لم أكن أعلم أنك أخته.
Unfortunately,
للأسف،
now I've fallen for you so hard I've lost my mind.
لقد وقعت في حبك بشدة لدرجة أنني فقدت عقلي.
Because you didn't answer your phone all day,
لأنك لم ترد على هاتفك طوال اليوم،
and Chen Yiyi told me you were at that mall,
وأخبرتني تشين ييي أنك كنت في ذلك المركز التجاري،
so I ran into the fire like a madman.
لذلك اندفعت نحو النار كالمجنون.
I don't even know what came over me,
لا أعرف حتى ما الذي أصابني.
doing a good deed I'd never have done in my life.
فعل الخير الذي لم أكن لأفعله في حياتي.
And the person I saved turned out to be...
والشخص الذي أنقذته اتضح أنه...
I'll give you a choice.
سأمنحك خياراً.
I can let go of my hatred for Wu Siyuan,
أستطيع أن أتخلى عن كراهيتي لـ وو سييوان،
but you have to make it up to me.
لكن عليك أن تعوضني عن ذلك.
Make it up to me with a whole lot of love.
عوضني عن ذلك بالكثير من الحب.
Only then can I forget
عندها فقط أستطيع أن أنسى
all that hatred.
كل هذا الكره.
Not interested?
غير مهتم؟
Then I don't mind keeping you locked up here.
إذن لا مانع لدي من إبقائك محبوساً هنا.
I'll love you properly,
سأحبك كما ينبغي،
and protect you properly too.
ويحميك بشكل صحيح أيضاً.
Thank you for making this concession for me,
شكراً لك على هذا التنازل من أجلي.
for giving my brother a chance to change.
لإعطائه أخي فرصة للتغيير.
I'll do my best to persuade him to turn himself in,
سأبذل قصارى جهدي لإقناعه بتسليم نفسه.
to confess
للاعتراف
everything he did to you,
كل ما فعله بك،
and atone for his past mistakes.
ويكفّر عن أخطائه الماضية.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I bought this for you.
اشتريت هذا من أجلك.
Go ahead and eat.
تفضل وتناول الطعام.
I know everything you said was a lie.
أعلم أن كل ما قلته كان كذباً.
You only said it to keep Nongyu from getting hurt.
قلت ذلك فقط لحماية نونغيو من الأذى.
So...
لذا...
So it doesn't matter to me at all.
لذا لا يهمني الأمر على الإطلاق.
Because I'm absolutely certain
لأنني متأكد تماماً
that what I feel for you is love.
إن ما أشعر به تجاهك هو الحب.
I want to take my place by your side,
أريد أن أكون بجانبك،
even if it's just once.
حتى لو كان ذلك لمرة واحدة فقط.
Loving me is hard.
حبي صعب.
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
I'm sure.
أنا متأكد.
I was sure an hour ago.
كنت متأكدًا قبل ساعة.
An hour ago?
قبل ساعة؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
So you're still leaving?
إذن ما زلت ستغادر؟
I'm not planning to leave.
لا أنوي المغادرة.
Chen Yiyi has been working on her thesis lately
تعمل تشين ييي على أطروحتها مؤخراً.
and needs some reference materials.
ويحتاج إلى بعض المواد المرجعية.
I'll sort them out and bring them to her tomorrow.
سأرتبها وأحضرها لها غداً.
Try not to get it wet these next couple of days.
حاول ألا تبللها خلال اليومين القادمين.
It should heal soon.
سيشفى قريباً.
It's really hard to imagine
من الصعب حقاً أن أتخيل
that you and Wu Siyuan are actually family.
أنك أنت و وو سيوان في الواقع عائلة.
You're really nothing alike.
أنتما مختلفان تماماً.
Sorry.
آسف.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
You don't need to apply it anymore.
لست بحاجة إلى تطبيقه بعد الآن.
Get some rest.
خذ قسطاً من الراحة.
Why don't we
لماذا لا نفعل ذلك؟
form a pact tonight?
هل نعقد اتفاقاً الليلة؟
Sorry.
آسف.
Did I hurt you?
هل آذيتك؟
I'm not very good at this.
أنا لستُ بارعاً جداً في هذا.
I got hurt here
لقد تعرضت للأذى هنا
because I was looking for you.
لأنني كنت أبحث عنك.
You have to take responsibility.
عليك أن تتحمل المسؤولية.
Help me rub it a bit.
ساعدني في تدليكه قليلاً.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪